a lot of your colleagues
много ваших сослуживцев
died my personally my seven
погибло моих лично моих семь
people Hello
человек Здравствуйте
Hello How are you doing Where are you from
Здравствуйте Как у вас дела Вы откуда
? I’m from the city of Khmelnitsk and you and
нормально Я из города Хмельницке а вы а
Russia St. Petersburg understood
Россия санкт-петербург понял петербуржец
native Petersburger Yes, why are you talking
коренной Да а чём общаетесь
here about everything more probably about
тут так обо всём больше наверное про
Ukraine about the war
Украину про войну
and you are a
а вы
former military man
военный бывший
understood
понял
And what And what is the
А что А что
former Yes, because I’m tired of this
бывший Да потому что надоела в эта
nonsense already and what’s tired of You don’t have
ерунда уже а что надоело У вас же нет
a war, it seems like everything is fine,
войны вроде как бы всё нормально у
you don’t have no We have a war If you
вас нет нет У нас есть война Если вы
provoke something like that, well,
спровоцировать на чтото то виду типа ну
what are you tired of What’s there  in St. Petersburg,
что вам надоело Что там Вот вы в Питере
what do you feel somehow, it’s
что ощущаете как-то это
all no, it was the Voskov airborne division.
всё нет была восковская дивизия десанта
I served there, as it were, and what
Я там служил как бы отслужил и что с
happened to them, I don’t know what happened to them, I
случилось с ними не знаю что случилось я
left. When the war began, that’s where the
ушёл Когда началась война вот там
Pskov paratroopers were very well
псковских десантника оче очень хорошо
defeated in Ukraine, but the truth is  the first days
разбили в Украине же правда в первые дни
I heard about this yes
я слышал об этом да
yes And that now many of your colleagues
да И что теперь много ваших сослуживцев
have died my personally my this person and
погибло моих лично моих сем человек а
this is From
это Из
how many No you asked my
скольки Нет вы спросили лично моих
friends personally I took this person from your
знакомых я отвел се человек из вашей
company this is or where it’s from not I’m
роты это или откуда там не я про ро
not talking about ro now not I  it’s just that my
сейчас не говорю не я просто го моих
friends and acquaintances are quite a
знакомых друзей се человек довольно
lot of people, quite a lot, yes, where did they
много довольно много да А где это они
die like that, listen, I don’t know exactly, they
погибли слушайте точно не знаю
said everything in different ways, but it
по-разному се говорили но вроде под
seems like a blast. That is, they were
бахну То есть их получается
actually disposed of in frontal
утилизировали фактически в лобовые
assaults, yes, unfortunately, like
штурмы да да к сожалению как собак
[ __ ] dogs, Prigozhin  said that they are
[__] там же Пригожин говорил что они
there How many are there 20 he stated that they
там Сколько там 20 он заявил что они
officially lost 20,000 fighters there
официально потеряли там 20.000 бойцов
This is what he stated clearly that there
Это то что он заявил ясно что больше
were more No he said only PMC
было Нет он заявил только чвк
Wagner only Vanya 20 we are not taking the calculation of
Вагнер только Ване 20 мы не берём расчёт
just the Russian army there another
просто армию России там ещё человек
20 thousand people at least
тысяч 20 как минимум
fell and  The most interesting thing is that you ask
упало и самое интересное вот спрашиваешь
like, why is this for what? They
типа а для чего вот ради чего за что Они
are fighting in Ukraine, what is the
воюют в Украине какая цель
ultimate goal? I don’t
конечная Я не
understand. Unfortunately, maybe if I
понимаю К сожалению может быть если я
understood, maybe I was some kind of
понимал бы я может быть был каким-то
great messiah, but I don’t understand, like, well, let’s say, Well,
великим мессией но я не понимаю типа ну
here we go  Bah, the price there is
допустим Ну вот взяли Бах ценой там
100,000 ski thousand there, like Russians, yes And
100000 ски тысяч там типа россиян да А
then what a No, I know what you’re
дальше что а Нет я знаю к чему вы
getting at if they took Bakhmut Yes, they
клоните если бы они взяли бахмут Да там
put 100,000 people there, but then they
100000 положили людей зато потом они по
showed on TV we took Bakhmut
телевизору показывали мы взяли бахмут
nuti, this is
нути это
military, why do you think this happened,
военный как думаете почему так случилось
what?  Well, you believed that Ukraine
что вот ну вы верили что Украина
would stand Yes, even before the war I believed And why
выстоит Да даже до войны верил А почему
for one simple reason
по одной простой причине то
that since
что так как
I Listen, you’re not filming me now
я Слушайте а вы сейчас меня не снимаете
I hope I’m filming, I’m filming on stream And you’re
Надеюсь снимаю снимаю я на стриме А вы
filming me, and I’m streaming now
снимаете меня да и Стрим сейчас веду
And then I’ll tell you a lot  I won’t be able to
А тогда я много вам сказать не смогу
then Yes
тогда Да
dose Listen Yes no
дози Слушайте Да нет
BC just let’s rephrase the phrase I’m
ВС просто скажем так перефрази фразу я
not a
не
military man and I’ll say So they underestimated the
военный и скажу Так что недооценили
opponent this time they thought that Europe
соперника это раз думали что Европа
would put a bolt on Ukraine this
положит болт на Украину это
two decided that like Crimea in the fourteenth
два решили что как Крым в четырнадцатом
year they took it without resistance this is three and they
году забрали без сопротивления это три а
got the WTO  the
ВТО получили по
teeth are all
зубам всё
rotten, the leadership of the Russian
прогнившие руководство российской
army is all
армии всё
stolen, there is no uniform, there is
разворована нет обмундирования нет
nothing from the republics of Russia
ничего с республик России
they are collecting there for the guys on their socks, [ __ ]
собирают там на ребят на носочки [__]
Well, I apologize for the swearing on their socks, there is something
Ну прошу прощения за мат на носочки там
else there, so that’s why
ещё на что-то поэтому поэтому мрак всё
it’s all darkness Putin is walking around It’s a whole bunch of these
Путин шагу Это вся куча этих
Roosters Unfortunately this is so  What do you
Петухов К сожалению это так А как как
think happened to Prigozhin,
думаете что случалось с пригожиным вот
he seemed to speak out so openly against the
он вроде ж выступал так открыто против
step
шагу
and Yes, it was such a comedy Yes, but the plane
и Да это было так комедия Да но самолёт
- This is no longer a comedy Well, the man is [ __ ] up, I
- Это уже не комедия Ну допизделся
understand, that is, if you think
человек понял то есть если вы думаете
that he is alive No No, of course I don’t
что он жив Нет Не не конечно не я
understand  he was removed because he suddenly
понимаю его убрали потому что он э вдруг
turned the Tanks around and went to Moscow. And what
развернул Танки и пошёл на Москву И как
does the force of the Wagner PMC have to
бы причём заним была сила чвк Вагнер все
do with it, that is, behind it there was a force of real
дела то есть за ней была сила реально
men with machine guns. And there already Mercenaries
мужики с автоматами А там уже Наёмники
are an irregular
это нерегулярная
army; there are already more trained people, more
армия там уже более обученные люди более
specialized, each in  your
специализированные каждый в своём
profile and that’s why this is such nonsense that’s why
профиле и поэтому вот такая ерунда
it was removed yes I understand you
поэтому его убрали
have some questions in
да понял у вас какие-то вопросы есть в
Ukraine listen to the question in Ukraine you
Украине слушайте вопрос в Украине знаете
only know probably a stupid question yes Well let
только наверно глупый вопрос да Ну пусть
me be a stupid person but I’ll
я буду глупым человеком но я его
ask it What do you think in your opinion eh
задам Как вы думаете на ваш взгляд э
how long  years or generations, we
через сколько лет или поколений мы снова
can be friends again Russia Ukraine m I think
можем дружить Россия Украина м я думаю
that as a
что в
result of this special military
результате этой специальной военной
operation, yes Russia as a geopolitical
операции да Россия как геополитическая
entity will cease to exist
сущность прекратить своё существование
since the Soviet Union Ceased to climb into
так как Советский Союз Прекратил в
Afghanistan, fizzled
Афганистан
out and completely collapsed
залез выдохся и развалился окончательно
economically Yes, and no, the question was
экономически Да также и нет вопрос был в
different and so  I’ll explain,
другом так вот я же я же объясню
look Booth It seems to me that after this
смотрите Бут Мне кажется что после этой
yes there will be a process of disintegration of the Russian
сво Да будет процесс распада Российской
Federation there will be new subjects Yes,
Федерации будут новые субъекты Да
national Republics will be
национальные Республики будут
states there will be regional ones there a
государствами будут региональные там
Siberian Federation there some kind of
Сибирская там Федерация какая-то там
Far Eastern Urals uh St. Petersburg
Дальневосточный Урал ээ Питер отдельно
will be separate, that is, there will be such regional
будет то есть будут такие региональные
states Yes  and separate relationships will already be built with them,
государства Да и с ними уже будут
depending on, say, how
в зависимости от скажем того как будет
everything will develop further, how they will be
всё развиваться дальше как они будут
built, you
строиться
know. I apologize, what is your
знае Я прошу прощения как вас
name Andrey Andrey With all due respect and
зовут Андрей Андрей При всем уважении и
with your thoughts, I understand what you are
при вашей мысли я понимаю о чём вы
talking about,
говорите
but unfortunately this will not work
но к сожалению такого не получится
Why is it that Russia doesn’t give a damn?
Почему дело в том что Россия не тся хрен
As if I didn’t want to Why did the
Как бы как бы и я не хотел Почему так
Soviet Union collapse? Who believed in the
Советский Союз распался кто Верил в
collapse of the Soviet Union once and
распад Советского Союза раз и развалился
didn’t collapse? No, there were other factors;
не Нет там были другие факторы здесь
this won’t happen here. It’s absolutely the
такого не произойдёт Т абсолютно такие
same, look once and for all  In the Soviet Union,
же смотрите раз и всё в Советском Союзе
no one even thought about it then, and
никто даже не думал потом раз и
literally within a year it was gone, you know,
буквально за год его не стало понимаете
it’s not even about Putin, then Putin will
дело даже не в Путине же тогда Путин
even leave, there are people behind him, it’s not that,
даже уйдёт есть за ним люди не дело в
look, contradictions are accumulating, contradictions,
том что смотрите накапливаются
interethnic contradictions, religious
межнациональные противоречия религиозные
contradictions, regional, and that is,
противоречия региональные да то есть
regions all-  after all, they have always been in
регионы вс-таки уже они всегда были в
our Russia, yes, but the war aggravates
нашей России да но война она обостряет
them, you know, and it’s precisely the repressive
их знаете а как раз репрессивный
potential Yes, it is dying in
потенциал Да он умирает в
Ukraine, that is, the center is weak No, it’s
Украине то есть центр слаб Нет это же
always been like this, some king got involved in
всегда было так сунулся какой-то царь в
some kind of war, weakened everything and
какую-то войнушку ослабил всё и
fell apart Well  I hope so, but
развалилось Ну я надеюсь прот так но
already look at Chechnya, Russia no longer
уже смотрите Чечню уже Россия не
controls Chechnya as a separate
контролирует Чечня как отдельное
state, Kadyrov is behaving ho Well,
государство себя ведёт ка Кадыров что хо
no, now it’s already open and everything is now
Ну нет сейчас уже открыто и всё сейчас
Republics are taking on more and
Республики принимают на себя больше и
more powers
больше полномочий
yes The Local Elite is starting to raise its
да Местная Элита начинает поднимать
head Yes, there is no local elite for a long time
голову Да уже нет местной элиты давно
Like no There are still local ones, there are always
Как нет Есть всё равно местная всегда
those who are there somewhere at the helm
есть то есть те кто там где-то у руля
somewhere in business and so on It does
где-то там при бизнесе и так дальше Всё
n’t matter For example, if in the Far East Yes, they have almost never been to Moscow But
ж в Москве почти никогда не бывали Зато
in Japan there or in China  regularly Yes,
в Японии там или в Китай регулярно Да
they are economically connected more with that
они экономически связаны больше с тем
region than with Moscow, for them Moscow
регионом чем с Москвой для них Москва -
is something like that; they wake up and
это что-то такое они просыпаются а
Moscow is still
Москва ещё
sleeping. Unfortunately, so that the regions lie down like
спит К сожалению чтобы регионы ложим тка
Siberia, or some of these distant
Сибирь да или какие-то вот эти дальние
regions
регионы
that came from
которые шли от
Russia, I know for you  I’ll say
России знаете я вам скажу у
they don’t have enough fortitude for one simple
них не хватит силы духу по одной простой
reason because it’s not because they
причине потому что не потому что они
’re afraid there, but Russia is not there, Putin is not there in
боятся там да Россия там Путина нет ни в
any case, because they think that
коем случае потому что они думают что
they will be left alone and they don’t look at all.
они останутся одни и всё они не смотри
The fact is that if we take the collapse of the
Дело в том что если мы возьмём распад
Soviet  The Union also had Republics that were
Советского Союза тоже были Республики
drivers like Lithuania, Latvia, Yes,
драйверы типа там Литва Латвия Да
Ukraine to some extent, Yes, the Baltic countries,
Украина в какой-то мере Да страны балтии
Georgia, too, that is, Ukraine even
грузи тоже то есть Украина даже позже
went later than them, that is, they proclaimed
них пошла да то есть они провозглашали
their independence, well, a year before, that
ну год до этого свою независимость то
is, they were drivers. Ukraine went Well,
есть они были драйверами Украина шла Ну
not the very first  yes But one of the first to
не самая первая да Но одной из первых
also move this agenda, Belarus has already
тоже двигала эту повестку Беларусь уже
gone with the flow and the countries there in Asia Yes,
пошла по течению и страны там Азии Да
too, they have already gone like Kazakhstan, in my opinion, the
тоже пошли уже типа Казахстан по-моему
very last one came out
самый последний вышел Да из Советского
Yes, it will be like that from the Soviet Union And here, that is, there will be
Союза так будет И тут то есть будут
republics and regions, drivers and
республики и регионы драйверы да
look Well, everything is already  pours out that's
смотрят Ну всё уже сыпется вот и
all Well, maybe it will be so Yes Okay Let's
всё Ну может быть так и будет
run All the best good
да Хорошо Давайте побегу Всего доброго
luck to you Okay just like that subscribe to us
удачи вам Окей вот так подпишись на ми
Telegram right now the VN
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
axis apok more and more respectfully YouTube
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through the skarg Orcs into your ban
загоняя нас через скарг Орки в твый бан
and the video is not showing too much  people are
и дуже багато видео не показуе людям
constantly not showing information about streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стримы
for this purpose so that we can write a Mali operational
тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
link directly at the same time and while there in
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegra okm video sche tezh Tsikava and
телегра окм видео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we are responsible for you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independantly in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
letter
пись
E
E